Vinicius Cainelli

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

vicainelli@gmail.com https://cainelli.rocks +55 (11) 982883353

ABOUT

My name is Vinicius and I'm a **Brazilian Frontend Developer** passionate about technology, innovation, music, and travel.

Strong knowledge and experience with **HTML**, **CSS**, and **Javascript**.

Knowledge and professional experience with AngularJS, Sass, Pug, Gulp, jQuery, Git, PHP, and MySQL.

Knowledge of VueJS, ES6, NodeJS, Laravel, AWS, Ubuntu, Serverless, and Docker.

EDUCATION

PGCERT, WEB ENGINEERING

SENAC • 2014 - 2015

BACHELOR OF ADVERTISING AND MARKETING

Mackenzie • 2005 - 2009

SKILLS

FRONTEND

.html, .css, .js, .vue, .sass, .pug

BACKEND

.php, .sql, .laravel

DEPLOYMENT

.aws, .digital-ocean

PROTOTYPING / DESIGN

.sketch, .adobe-photoshop

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

CO-FOUNDER & HALF STACK DEVELOPER

Menyoo :: 2016 - Present

Menyoo is my side project, it's a SAAS platform for bars and restaurants. I build the beta version of Menyoo platform using pure PHP with HTML/CSS/JS. Now I'm developing a new version using Laravel and VueJS.

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Mandaê :: 2016 - 2018

At Mandaê, besides writing code, I also create and develop solutions that are helping hundreds of customers.

- Build UI applications using AngularJS and Bootstrap
- Develop responsive UIs while working directly with Design team
- Responsible for the development of the new institutional website
- Store and consume data from Restful Web APIs and Services

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Bcash / PayU :: 2013 - 2016

At Bcash, I worked in two different teams, Product and IT.

- Prototype new concepts along with a UX Designer
- A/B testings to improve a checkout conversions
- Hotsites and emails for marketing campaigns
- Rebranding project: From Bcash to PayU.